<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">ArcanaCard</string>
    <string name="app_loc">arcanacard.com</string>
    <string name="app_weblink">http://tereslogica.com</string>
    <string name="activity_topics">Topics</string>
    <string name="activity_new">Create Topic</string>
    <string name="activity_qrviewer">View QRCodes</string>
    <string name="menu_testtoken">Debug Scan Test</string>
    <string name="menu_sort">Sort Topics</string>
    <string name="menu_licenses">Licenses</string>
    <string name="menu_howtos">Replay Howtos</string>
    <string name="menu_website">Website</string>
    <string name="menu_new_clearfill">Clear Items</string>
    <string name="menu_new_autofill_shakespeare">Shakespeare</string>
    <string name="menu_new_autofill_julesverneEN">Jules Verene (en)</string>
    <string name="menu_new_autofill_julesverneFR">Jules Verene (fr)</string>
    <string name="dialog_howto">Howto</string>
    <string name="dialog_selectsorting">Change Sorting</string>
    <string name="dialog_noscanner">Scanner app (zxing) not found.</string>
    <string name="dialog_nonativelib">Installation error: native library not found.</string>
    <string name="dialog_nomultiline">Multiline text not allowed.</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_decode">New message decoded</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_clue">New clue found</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_topic">New topic found</string>
    <string name="dialog_newtopic">New topic created</string>
    <string name="dialog_err_encode">There was an encoding failure.</string>
    <string name="dialog_err_decode">There was a decoding failure.</string>
    <string name="sharelist_messagedecodeerror">Unable to decode message.</string>
    <string name="sharelist_needmorekeys">More keys needed to unlock message.</string>
    <string name="sharelist_nomessage">Message not yet scanned.</string>
    <string name="button_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="button_gotit">Got it!</string>
    <string name="button_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_no">No</string>
    <string name="button_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="button_sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="button_new">New</string>
    <string name="button_purge">Purge</string>
    <string name="button_share">Share</string>
    <string name="button_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="button_more">More</string>
    <string name="button_less">Less</string>

    <string name="text_howto_topic">
ArcanaCards are minted in groups called \'Topics\'. There are two types of cards: message cards and key cards. To
 reveal a hidden message you need the message card and atleast two of the key cards (exactly
 how many will depend on the \'locks\' setting when the topic was minted). ArcanaCard groups
 cards together when you scan them and shows you how many more you might need before you can
 reveal the hidden message.\n
\nOn the main screen the topics are listed, each with a set of letter indicators at the top
 right. The indicators are:\n
\n* M nnnK nnnL nnnT\n
\n\'*\' Means you can read the hidden message because you have the message card and enough of the keys to unlock it (short-press on the topic to read the message),\n
\n\'M\' Means you have scanned the message code (but you may not be able to read it if you don\'t have enough keys),\n
\nnnnK How many keys you have for this topic (nnn is shorthand for the number of keys you\'ve collected),\n
\nnnnL How many locks are on the message. To unlock a hidden message you need the message and this many keys (nnn is the number locks on the message),\n
\nnnnT The total number of keys that were made for this message.\n
\nYou can long-press on a topic to access other topic-related options, but to get
 started press the NEW button to create your first topic.
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_new">
\'Keys\' are the number of codes that will be created.\n
\n\'Locks\' are the number of keys that must be scanned to reveal your hidden message.\n
\n\'Clues\' can be attached to keys and can be read as soon as a key is scanned.\n
\nChoose clues that create an interesting game mechanic, ie. the locations of other keys or
 portions of a text. Use the menu autofill options to get started with some quote-based
 games from some public domain texts.
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_test">
Great work, you\' made a new topic. You can test out your new topic with a long-press and
 selecting \'View QRCodes\' (if you have a friend with ArcanaCard they can try scanning the
 codes) or you can select \'Export for printing\'.\n
\nExporting your topic to a PC and printing the codes is the way to take ArcanaCard out
 into the real world.
    </string>

    <string name="text_features_limitedversion">
This version of ArcanaCard is restricted to 7 keys, 7 locks and 63 character
 messages and clues.</string>

    <string name="text_eula">
TLDR: This software is a toy. Don\'t do anything serious with it.\n
\nBy using this software you accept the following:\n
\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\" AND ANY EXPRESS
 OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
 WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
 ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE
 LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
 CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR
 BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
 WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
 OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
 EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    </string>
    <string name="text_licenses">
This software contains components developed by tereslogica &lt;tereslogica@gmail.com&gt;
 as well as the following licensed components:
\n\npegwit, Public Domain, License granted by George Barwood  &lt;george.barwood@dial.pipex.com&gt;,
 Paulo S.L.M. Barreto &lt;pbarreto@uninet.com.br&gt; and Mr. Tines &lt;tines@windsong.demon.co.uk&gt;
\n\nsha1, Public Domain, License granted by Steve Reid &lt;steve@edmweb.com&gt;\n
\n\nzxing, Copyright 2007 ZXing Authors, Apache 2.0 License, http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html\n
\n\nThis application implements a version of Shamir\'s Secret Sharing Algorithm
 with 56 bit polynomial coefficients to reveal a 56 bit rc4 cipher key to decrypt the hidden
 message. Topic tokens are signed with a per-topic single-use 96 bit authentication key. Arithmetic
 for the polynomial evaluation and for the authentication signature are performed on the
 non-prime binary-field GF(2^112), a Koblitz curve.\n
    </string>

</resources>
