<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">ArcanaCard</string>
    <string name="app_loc">arcanacard.com</string>
    <string name="app_weblink">http://tereslogica.com</string>
    <string name="activity_topics">Topics</string>
    <string name="activity_new">Create Topic</string>
    <string name="activity_qrviewer">View QRCodes</string>
    <string name="menu_testtoken">Debug Scan Test</string>
    <string name="menu_sort">Sort Topics</string>
    <string name="menu_licenses">Licenses</string>
    <string name="menu_howtos">Replay howto</string>
    <string name="menu_website">Website</string>
    <string name="menu_clearfill">Clear items</string>
    <string name="menu_autofill">Autofill</string>
    <string name="menu_cryptoinfo">Crypto info</string>
    <string name="dialog_howto">Howto</string>
    <string name="dialog_selectsorting">Change Sorting</string>
    <string name="dialog_noscanner">Scanner app (zxing) not found.</string>
    <string name="dialog_nonativelib">Installation error: native library not found.</string>
    <string name="dialog_nomultiline">Multiline text not allowed.</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_decode">New message decoded</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_clue">New clue found</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_topic">New topic found</string>
    <string name="dialog_info_autofill">Select Autofill</string>
    <string name="dialog_newtopic">New topic created</string>
    <string name="dialog_err_encode">There was an encoding failure.</string>
    <string name="dialog_err_decode">There was a decoding failure.</string>
    <string name="sharelist_messagedecodeerror">Unable to decode message.</string>
    <string name="sharelist_needmorekeys">More keys needed to unlock message.</string>
    <string name="sharelist_nomessage">Message not yet scanned.</string>
    <string name="button_ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="button_gotit">Got it!</string>
    <string name="button_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_no">No</string>
    <string name="button_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="button_sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="button_new">New</string>
    <string name="button_purge">Purge</string>
    <string name="button_share">Share</string>
    <string name="button_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="button_more">More</string>
    <string name="button_less">Less</string>

    <string name="text_howto_intro">
ArcanaCard allows you to make short hidden messages that require multiple keys to reveal.
 You \'mint\' your message with it\'s keys, ie. they become a set. Each set is called a \'Topic\' and
 although topics have cryptic names you can put a clue on the message or any of the keys.
\n\nTo reveal a message you must have the message card and at least two of the key
 cards; exactly how many keys you require will depend on the \'locks\' setting when the topic was minted.
\n\nArcanaCard shares topics using QRCodes and so needs you to install a QRCode scanning app,
 like ZXing or Google Goggles. As well, it works best with physically printed QRCodes that
 you can trade between friends or hide for friends to find.
\n\nTo get started press the NEW BUTTON to create your first topic.
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_new">
You create a new topic with a message, hidden by a number of locks and unlockable using some number of keys.
\n\n\'Keys\' are the number of completely interchangeable keys that will be created. It can be larger than the number of locks on a message but not smaller.
\n\n\'Locks\' are the number of keys that someone must possess to reveal your hidden message. They must have your message card as well!
\n\n\'Clues\' can be attached to keys and can be read as soon as a key is scanned. Clues are
 not encrypted. Choose clues that are interesting or helpful, ie. the locations of other
 keys or perhaps portions of a text.
\n\nUse the AUTOFILL MENU to get started with some quote-based games from some public domain texts.
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_autofill">
Autofill will create an example game for you using some works that are in the
 public domain.
\n\nThis kind of game requires you to guess the title of an author\'s book or play from
 only seeing famous portions of its text. You lose if you collect enough keys to unlock it.
\n\nAutofill works with your current key and lock settings, so you can customize the difficulty of each game.
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_greatwork">
Great work, you\'ve made a new topic!
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_indicators">
Each card contains information about the set it was minted with. ArcanaCard can show you this
 information and how many cards of each topic you currently have. The main screen shows
 these indicators in the top right of each topic:
\n\n* M nK nL nT
\n\n\'*\' Means you can read the hidden message because you have the message card and enough of the keys to unlock it,
\n\n\'M\' Means you have scanned the message card (but you may not be able to read it if you don\'t have enough keys!),
\n\n\'nK\' Shows that you have collected \'n\' keys for a particular topic,
\n\n\'nL\' Shows how many locks are on the message. To unlock a hidden message you would need the message card and \'n\' keys,
\n\n\'nT\' Shows that there are a total of \'n\' keys made for this message.
    </string>

    <string name="text_howto_test">
On the main screen you can short-press on a topic to read a message or long-press to access
 other topic-related options where you can view the QRCodes or send them to a PC for printing.
\n\nExporting your topic to a PC and printing the codes is the way to take ArcanaCard out
 into the real world.
    </string>

    <string name="text_features_limitedversion">
This version of ArcanaCard is restricted to 7 keys, 7 locks and 63 character
 messages and clues.</string>

    <string name="text_eula">
TLDR: This software is a toy. Don\'t do anything serious with it.\n
\nBy using this software you accept the following:\n
\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\" AND ANY EXPRESS
 OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
 WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
 ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE
 LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
 CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR
 BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
 WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE
 OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE,
 EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
    </string>
    <string name="text_licenses">
This software contains components developed by tereslogica &lt;tereslogica@gmail.com&gt;
 as well as the following licensed components:
\n\npegwit, Public Domain, License granted by George Barwood  &lt;george.barwood@dial.pipex.com&gt;,
 Paulo S.L.M. Barreto &lt;pbarreto@uninet.com.br&gt; and Mr. Tines &lt;tines@windsong.demon.co.uk&gt;
\n\nsha1, Public Domain, License granted by Steve Reid &lt;steve@edmweb.com&gt;
\n\nzxing, Copyright 2007 ZXing Authors, Apache 2.0 License, http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html
\n\nPortions of works by William Shakespeare, Jules Verne and Beatrix Potter all Public Domain.
    </string>
    <string name="text_cryptoinfo">
This application stores hidden messages using the rc4 cipher with a 56 bit key and uses
 Shamir\'s Secret Sharing Algorithm with 56 bit coefficients for key reconstruction. Topic
 tokens are signed with per-topic, single-use 96 bit authentication keys. All field
 arithmetic is performed on the non-prime binary-field GF(2^112). This application claims
 export-restriction exempt status under Wassenaar 5.A.2.a.1.a and US EAR 5x992.
    </string>

</resources>
